Guide to the American Theological Library Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Board of Index, Series IV
  - Reports
    - Codifying Board Minutes, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 524)
    - Multi-Author Works, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 525)
    - Organizational Analysis, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 526)
    - RIO and Questionnaire (Box 44, Folder 527)
    - RIO-RIT Update, 1979-1982 (Box 44, Folder 528-529)
    - Computer Hardware and Software Needs (Box 44, Folder 530)
  - Periodical Index
    - Elaboration of Proposal (Box 44, Folder 531)
    - Minutes, Reports, Notes, 1947-1954; 1957-1962; 1964-1975; 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 532)
    - Proposal for Establishment of a Religious Periodical Index; Questionnaire; Report, 1953-1955 (Box 45, Folder 533)
    - Proposals to Foundations; Correspondence and Drafts, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 534)
    - Personnel Manual, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 535)
  - Correspondence and Reports
    - Miscellaneous, 1975-1986 (Box 45, Folder 536-541)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 542-543)
  - Correspondence
    - Periodical Index, 1952-1972 (Box 46, Folder 544-549)
    - General, 1973-1979 (Box 46, Folder 550)
    - Periodical Index, 1975-1979 (Box 47, Folder 551)
    - General, 1980-1985 (Box 47, Folder 552-556)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 557)
  - Materials added 2006
    - Agendas and background papers for meetings, 1979-1983 (Box 122, Folder 31-39)
    - Computer software considerations, 1970-1971 (Box 122, Folder 40)
    - Editor's reports to Board, 1970-1979 (Box 122, Folder 41-49)
    - Index Board reports to Board of Directors, 1981, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 50-51)
    - Minutes project, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 52)
    - Reports re. Index to Religious Periodical Literature (IRPL), 1972-1976 (Box 122, Folder 53-54)
    - NEH Grant to fund Religion Index Two, Multi-Author Works, 1970-1975, 1978-1983 (Box 122, Folder 55-56)
    - Pre-publication announcement for Religion Index Two (RIT), 1977 (Box 122, Folder 57)
    - Festschriften Project, 1979-1980 (Box 122, Folder 58)
    - Doctor of Ministry Project, 1979-1983 (Box 122, Folder 59)
    - ATLA Religion Indexes Keying Guide, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 60)
    - Search for in-house computer system, 1980 (Box 122, Folder 61)
    - Charts of suggested reorganization of Religion Index staff, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 62)
    - Personnel policies and job descriptions, 1972-1983 (Box 122, Folder 63-64)
    - Drafts of personnel policies, 1980-1983 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Re. Fay Dickinson, Editor, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Re. Fay Dickinson, Editor - restricted until 2050, 1982 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence of Chairperson, Calvin Schmidt, 1971-1974 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence of Chairperson, R.Grant Bracewell, 1971-1983 (Box 123, Folder 4-5)
    - Correspondence between Chairperson and ATLA Executive Board, 1979-1980 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence between Chairperson and editors, 1978-1983 (Box 123, Folder 7-8)
    - Correspondence regarding NEH Grant for Religion Index Two, 1978-1979 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence between Chairperson and members of Board of Index, 1979-1983 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with/ re. DIALOG, 1980-1983 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with /re. Bibliographic Retrieval Services (BRS), 1980-1984 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Report re. Religion Indexes by Peat, Marwick, Mitchell Co., 1984 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Executive Director's report re. Board of Index, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Strategic Plan for Indexes and Preservation, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 15-16)
    - Religion Indexes Thesaurus, 1980 Nov 4 (Box 123, Folder 17-20)
    - Religion Indexes Thesaurus - for in-house use of indexers, 1980 Feb (Box 123, Folder 21-22)
    - Religion Indexes Thesaurus, 3rd edition, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - Religion Indexes Thesaurus, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 24-25)
    - Religion Indexes Thesaurus, 4th edition, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 26)
    - Religion Indexes Thesaurus, published edition, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - Religion Indexes Thesaurus (Box 123, Folder 28-30)
    - Bibliography of Festscriften in Religion Published Since 1960: Preliminary Checklist, 1972, 1975 (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
    - Religion Index Two: 1970-1975: 2 part bibliography of books indexed as of June 3, 1980 and books not yet examined but considered in scope (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Evangelicalism and Fundatmentalism: A Bibliography Selected from the ATLA Religion Database: 1st Revised Edition, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 4-5)
    - Culture and Religion: A Bibliography Selected from the ATLA Religion Database: 2nd Revised Edition, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 6-8)
    - Women and Religion: A Bibliography Selected from the ATLA Religion Database: 3rd Revised Edition, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 9-11)
    - Eastern Christianity: A Bibliography Selected from the ATLA Religion Database: Revised Edition, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 12-14)
    - Research in Ministry: An Index to Doctor of Ministry Project Reports and Theses Submitted by Reporting ATS Schools, 1981, 1982, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 15-17)
    - Seminaries and Theological Education: A Bibliography Selected From the ATLA Religion Database: 3rd Revised Edition, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 18-19)
    - Luther and Lutheranism: A Bibliography Selected from the ATLA Religion Database: Revised Edition, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 20-22)
    - Bibliography of Missiology: Manual for Sub-editors: 1st Edition, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - The Reformed Traditions, 16th-19th Centuries: A Bibliography Selected from theATLA Religion Database, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 24-25)
    - Instructions for Use of the ATLA Religion Database Index Computer Programs: Partially Revised Edition, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 26)
    - IBRR Style Sheet: Retrospect Project: Book Reviews, 1949-1974: Version 1.4, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 27)
    - Online Searching in Religion: A Continuing Education Workshop, 1988, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 28-29)
    - Planning Grant Proposal to the Lilly Endowment in support of retrospective indexing and preservation of journal literature in religion 1900-1948, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 30)
    - Advisory Committee on Denominational Bibliographies, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 31)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP): proposal to Pew Charitable Trusts, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - ICLDP: questionnaire, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - ICLDP: Mission and scope statements, ca.1989-1990 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - ICLDP: correspondence, press releases, proposal, financial records, 1989-1990 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - ICLDP: Advisory Committee meetings, 1989-1992 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - ICLDP: Surveys to nominate institutions, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - ICLDP: Non-Western Christian literature collections survey, 1989-1990 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - ICLDP: Corporate sponsors list, ca. 1990 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - ICLDP: Editorial Advisory Committee correspondence and meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - ICLDP: Sample records distributed to Editorial Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - ICLDP: On-site indexing: Union Theological Seminary (VA), Graduate Theological Union, Yale Divinity School, 1989-1990 (Box 125, Folder 11-13)
    - Research in Ministry (RIM), 1985-1990 (Box 126, Folder 1-6)
    - Religion Index One (RIO): grant application, prospectus, 1988-1991 (Box 126, Folder 7-8)
    - Brochure: A Special ATLA Product Discount Offer, 1990 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Hiring of new editor, 1983 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - Reports from Business Manager of Index, 1982-1983 (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - Communications between Chairman of Index Board and ATLA treasurer, 1979-1981 (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - Communications between Chairman of Index Board and Index staff, 1979-1981 (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - Foundations approached for retrospective indexing project, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 42)
  - Materials added 2015
    - Budgets, 1983-1986 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Steering Committee / Advisory Committee on Denominational Bibliographies, 1989-1990 (Box 134, Folder 2)
- Board of Microtext, Series V
  - General Records
    - Formation, 1954-1961 (Box 48, Folder 558)
    - Policy (Box 48, Folder 559)
    - Job Description, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 560)
    - Questionnaire and Mailing, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 561)
    - Contracts with University Microfilms, Inc., 1955-1977 (Box 48, Folder 562)
    - Publishing Agreements, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 563)
    - List of Institutions (Box 48, Folder 564)
    - Incorporation, 1956-1976 (Box 48, Folder 565)
  - Financial Records
    - Expenses, 1957-1984 (Box 48, Folder 566-568)
    - Funding, 1965-1971, 1980-1981 (Box 48, Folder 569-570)
    - Grants: NEH, Lilly, DHEW (Box 48, Folder 571)
    - Quarterly Statements, 1982-1984 (Box 48, Folder 572)
    - Notes, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 573)
    - Selection of Titles for Microtext Publication, 1953-1980 (Box 49, Folder 574)
    - Lists of Microfilms Available, 1960-1983 (Box 49, Folder 575-578)
    - Problems, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 579)
    - List of Microfilms Available, 1971-1975 (Box 49, Folder 580)
    - Periodical Lists, 1956-1972 (Box 49, Folder 581-584)
  - Meetings
    - Minutes, 1968, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 585-586)
    - Minutes and Related Material, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 587-588)
    - Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 50, Folder 589)
  - Reports
    - General, 1958; 1961; 1967-1969 (Box 50, Folder 590)
    - Libraries, 1962-1967 (Box 50, Folder 591-595)
    - General, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 596)
    - Mid-Year, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 597)
    - Annual, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 598)
    - Cooperative Preservation of Microfilm, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 599)
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1956-1977 (Box 50, Folder 600)
    - Programs, 1956-1958 (Box 51, Folder 601)
    - General, 1956-1961 (Box 51, Folder 602-603)
    - Decherd Turner, 1957-1962 (Box 51, Folder 604)
    - Methodista, 1958-1966 (Box 51, Folder 605)
    - Reprint Permission, 1960-1971 (Box 51, Folder 606)
    - General, 1960-1961 (Box 51, Folder 607)
    - Methodistica from Wesley Seminary, 1962-1969 (Box 51, Folder 608)
    - General, 1962-1963 (Box 51, Folder 609)
    - Cosby Brinkley, 1963-1972 (Box 51, Folder 610)
    - Inquiries and Orders, 1964-1967 (Box 51, Folder 611)
    - General, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 612)
    - Methodist Material, 1965-1973 (Box 51, Folder 613)
    - General, 1965-1968 (Box 51, Folder 614)
    - Library of Congress, 1965-1978 (Box 52, Folder 615)
    - Presbyterian Historical Society, 1967-1978 (Box 52, Folder 616)
    - Inquiries and Orders, 1968-1973 (Box 52, Folder 617)
    - John Ness, 1969-1973 (Box 52, Folder 618)
    - Charles Willard and Raymond Morris, 1970-1974 (Box 52, Folder 619)
    - General, 1970-1975 (Box 52, Folder 620)
    - Official, 1970-1981 (Box 52, Folder 621)
    - Permissions, 1973-1976 (Box 52, Folder 622)
    - University Microfilms, Xerox, 1973-1976 (Box 52, Folder 623)
    - Copyright, 1973-1976 (Box 53, Folder 624)
    - General, 1973-1979 (Box 53, Folder 625)
    - Cosby Brinkley, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 626)
    - World Council of Churches, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 627)
    - Permissions, 1975-1978 (Box 53, Folder 628)
    - General, 1975-1979 (Box 53, Folder 629)
    - Harvard, 1976-1981 (Box 53, Folder 630)
    - Cataloging, 1977-1980 (Box 53, Folder 631-633)
    - Scholar Press, 1977-1980 (Box 54, Folder 634)
    - General, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 635)
    - Historical Foundation, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 636)
    - Foundation, 1980-1985 (Box 54, Folder 637)
    - Princeton, 1981-1986 (Box 54, Folder 638)
    - General, 1981-1984 (Box 54, Folder 639-640)
    - ISBN (Box 54, Folder 641)
  - Materials added 2006
    - Prospectus: Cooperative Microfilm Project on Religion and Theology, 1977 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - List of Microfilms Available, 1981 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Serials Catalog, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 16)
- Board of Directors, Series VI
  - Minutes, reports, agendas, 1972 Jan-1979 Jan (Box 55, Folder 642-661)
  - Minutes, reports, agendas, 1979 Jun-1982 Jan (Box 56, Folder 662-676)
  - Minutes, reports, agendas, 1982 Jun-1984 Jun (Box 57, Folder 677-688)
  - Minutes, reports, agendas, 1984 Jun-1986 Jun (Box 58, Folder 689-702)
  - Minutes, 1986 Jun-1990 Feb (Box 59, Folder 703-710)
  - Minutes, 1990 Jun (Box 61, Folder 711)
  - Reports
    - General, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 723)
    - By-Laws, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 724)
    - Treasurer, 1977-1982 (Box 61, Folder 725)
    - General, 1977, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 726-728)
    - Conference, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 729)
    - Annual, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 730)
    - General, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 731-733)
  - Correspondence
    - Chapters, 1971-1980 (Box 62, Folder 743)
    - General, 1974-1978 (Box 62, Folder 744-746)
    - Preservation, 1978-1984 (Box 62, Folder 747)
    - General, 1978-1982 (Box 62, Folder 748-749)
    - Council on National Library and Information Associations, 1979-1982 (Box 62, Folder 750)
    - Mid-Winter Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 751)
    - General, 1979-1983 (Box 62, Folder 752-755)
    - American Theological Society, 1983-1984 (Box 62, Folder 756)
    - Agendas and Reports, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 757)
    - General, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 758)
    - Whole Board, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 759)
    - General, 1984-1994 (Box 63, Folder 760-766)
- Board of Preservation, Series VII
  - Reports
    - Project 2000, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 771)
    - General, 1985-1986 Feb (Box 64, Folder 772-775)
    - National Endowment for Humanities Grant Request, 1986 May (Box 64, Folder 776)
    - General, 1986 Jul (Box 64, Folder 777-778)
    - Director's Annual, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 779)
    - General, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 780-781)
    - Special Board Meeting, October 1987 (Box 65, Folder 782)
  - Reports and Correspondence
    - General, 1981-1994 (Box 65, Folder 783-790)
  - Materials added 2006
    - Lutheran School of Theology, Chicago, rental contract, 1985-1988 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Forms for reimbursement, purchase orders, etc., ca. 1986 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Job descriptions, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Ad Hoc Committee for the Preservation of Theological Library Materials - final report, 1981 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence and contracts with Micro Publications Systems, 1985-1987 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence and contract for microfilming services with the Photoduplication Department of the University of Chicago, 1985-1987 (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Brochure re. microfilm operations at University of Chicago, ca. 1986 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Office procedures manual (draft), 1986 (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Frye consultancy report on Preservation Board, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - Summary Statement on the Preservation Project, ca. 1987 (Box 125, Folder 26)
    - Report by consultant Conrad Cherry on the Indexes and Preservation Project, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 27)
    - Strategic planning for 1988-1989, 1987-1988 (Box 125, Folder 28)
    - Monograph Preservation Program: Preliminary bibliography: General denominational history, 1986 (Box 125, Folder 29)
    - Biblical texts and reference works collection catalog: Phase III Supplemental titles, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 30)
    - Monograph Preservation Program: Phase O catalog, 1985 (Box 125, Folder 31)
    - List of microforms available, 1985 (Box 125, Folder 32)
    - Catalog of microfilms available, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 33)
    - Catalog supplement (Phase 2), 1988 (Box 125, Folder 34)
    - Serials catalog, 1988, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 35-36)
    - Brochure for Church History Microfiche Collection, ca. 1989 (Box 125, Folder 37)
    - Brochure: Preservation Filming in Religion (PREFIR): Serials Preservation, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 38)
    - Preservation Filming in Religion (PREFIR):On-demand Monograph Filming, 1989-1990 (Box 125, Folder 39)
    - PREFIR catalog, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 46)
    - Biblical Texts and Reference Works Collections: a Prospectus, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 40)
    - Minutes, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 30)
  - Materials added 2015
    - Board meeting materials, 1985-1988 (Box 134, Folder 4-10)
    - Correspondence of John Bollier, 1984-1988 (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence of Robert Markham, 1985-1992 (Box 135, Folder 1-17)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 136, Folder 1-4)
    - Rough draft directory of potential subscribers to Monograph Preservation Program, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Technical specifications, 1988-1991 (Box 136, Folder 6-9)
    - Consultation, January 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Brochures, article, 1988, no date (Box 136, Folder 17)
- Related Organizations and Programs, Series VIII
  - American Association of Theological Schools
    - Biennial Meeting Programs, 1948-1956 (Box 66, Folder 791)
    - Library Accreditation Standards, 1948-1972 (Box 66, Folder 792)
    - Correspondence re. ATS National Consultation on Theological Library Cooperation, 1978 (Box 125, Folder 49)
    - "Aids to a Theological Library", 1958 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - American Library Association
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1948-1977 (Box 66, Folder 793)
    - Handbook, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 794)
    - Correspondence, Articles and Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 795)
  - Association of Theological Schools
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1973-1980 (Box 66, Folder 796-797)
  - Chicago Area Theological Libraries Association
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1966-1975 (Box 66, Folder 798)
    - Conference Material, 1975-1982 (Box 66, Folder 799)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 66, Folder 800)
    - Correspondence, Directories, Newsletters, Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Commission on Preservation and Access
    - Correspondence and reports, 1986-1990 (Box 136, Folder 12-13)
  - Cooperative Online Serials Program
    - Newsletter, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 801)
  - Council on Library Resources
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1957-1971 (Box 66, Folder 802)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Council of National Library Associations Inc.
    - Minutes, 1964-1968 (Box 66, Folder 803)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1979 (Box 67, Folder 804)
    - Minutes, 1969-1976 (Box 67, Folder 805)
  - Council on the Study of Religion
    - Reports, 1973-1978 (Box 67, Folder 806)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1979 (Box 67, Folder 807-808)
  - Inforonics
    - Sample Publication (Box 67, Folder 809)
  - International Association of Theological Libraries
    - Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 810)
  - International Commission on English in Liturgy
    - Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box 67, Folder 811)
  - National Endowment of the Humanities
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 67, Folder 812)
  - Presbyterian Library Association
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1959-1983 (Box 68, Folder 813-815)
  - Presbyterian and Reformed Library Association
    - Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 68, Folder 816)
  - Princeton Institute for Theological Libraries
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1979-1983 (Box 68, Folder 817)
  - Special Library Association
    - Index, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 818)
  - Union Theological Seminary in Virginia
    - Human Rights and Bill of Rights, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 819)
  - Universal Series and Book Exchange Inc. (formerly United States Book Exchange)
    - Report and Bulletin, 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 820)
    - Reports, 1971-1978 (Box 68, Folder 821)
- Conferences, Series IX
  - General
    - Original Minute Book, 1947-1954 (Box 69, Folder 822)
    - Index to the Proceedings of the Annual Meetings of ATLA, 1947-1966 (Box 69, Folder 823)
    - Bibliographical Essays Appearing in Summary of Proceedings, 1947-1971 (Box 69, Folder 824)
    - Handbook for conferences of the ATLA, 1985 (Box 125, Folder 42)
  - First Annual Conference - Louisville
    - Proceedings, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 825)
    - Conference Material, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 826)
  - Second Annual Conference - Dayton
    - Proceedings, 1948 (Box 69, Folder 827)
    - Conference Material, 1948 (Box 69, Folder 828)
  - Third Annual Conference - Chicago
    - Proceedings, 1949 (Box 69, Folder 829)
    - Conference Material, 1949 (Box 69, Folder 830)
  - Fourth Annual Conference - Columbus
    - Proceedings, 1950 (Box 69, Folder 831)
    - Conference Material, 1950 (Box 69, Folder 832)
  - Fifth Annual Conference - Rochester
    - Proceedings, 1951 (Box 69, Folder 833)
    - Conference Material, 1951 (Box 69, Folder 834)
  - Sixth Annual Conference - Louisville
    - Proceedings, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 835)
    - Conference Material, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 836)
  - Seventh Annual Conference - Evanston
    - Proceedings, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 837)
    - Conference Material, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 838)
  - Eighth Annual Conference - Chicago
    - Proceedings, 1954 (Box 70, Folder 839)
    - Conference Material, 1954 (Box 70, Folder 840)
  - Ninth Annual Conference - New York
    - Proceedings, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 841)
    - Conference Material, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 842)
  - Tenth Annual Conference - Berkeley
    - Proceedings, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 843)
    - Conference Material, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 844)
  - Eleventh Annual Conference - Fort Worth
    - Proceedings, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 845)
    - Conference Material, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 846)
  - Twelfth Annual Conference - Boston
    - Proceedings, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 847)
    - Conference Material, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 848)
  - Thirteenth Annual Conference - Toronto
    - Proceedings, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 849)
    - Conference Material, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 850)
  - Fourteenth Annual Conference - St. Paul
    - Proceedings, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 851)
    - Conference Material, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 852)
  - Fifteenth Annual Conference - Washington, D.C.
    - Proceedings, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 853)
    - Conference Material, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 854)
  - Sixteenth Annual Conference - Hartford
    - Proceedings, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 855)
    - Conference Material, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 856)
  - Seventeenth Annual Conference - Mill Valley, CA
    - Proceedings, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 857)
    - Conference Material, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 858)
  - Eighteenth Annual Conference - Kansas City
    - Proceedings, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 859)
    - Conference Material, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 860)
  - Nineteenth Annual Conference - New York
    - Proceedings, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 861)
    - Conference Material, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 862)
  - Twentieth Annual Conference
    - Proceedings, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 863)
    - Conference Material, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 864)
  - Twenty-first Annual Conference - Chicago
    - Proceedings, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 865)
    - Conference Material, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 866)
  - Twenty-second Annual Conference - St. Louis
    - Proceedings, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 867)
    - Conference Material, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 868)
  - Twenty-third Annual Conference - Pittsburgh
    - Proceedings, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 869)
    - Conference Material, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 870)
  - Twenty-fourth Annual Conference - New Orleans
    - Proceedings, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 871)
    - Conference Material, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 872)
  - European Conference
    - Plans Abandoned, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 873)
  - Twenty-fifth Annual Conference - Pasadena
    - Proceedings, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 874)
    - Conference Material, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 875)
    - Workshop on Library Clustering, 1971 (Box 125, Folder 47)
  - Twenty-sixth Annual Conference - Waterloo
    - Proceedings, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 876)
    - Conference Material, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 877)
  - Twenty-seventh Annual Conference - Bethlehem, PA
    - Proceedings, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 878)
    - Conference Material, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 879)
  - Twenty-eighth Annual Conference - Denver
    - Proceedings, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 880)
    - Conference Material, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 881)
  - Twenty-ninth Annual Conference - South Hamilton, MA